<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supervised Learning on Kasun Malwenna</title>
    <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/tags/supervised-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supervised Learning on Kasun Malwenna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/tags/supervised-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flight Fare Prediction: Let&#39;s Find the Best Rates</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Due to the recent global pandemic, prices of air travel have increased significantly, causing financial challenges for airlines worldwide. As a result, travel disruptions have ensued, leading to 2.3 million job losses in the aviation sector. Prior to the pandemic, air tickets were already subject to price fluctuations due to the competitiveness of the aviation industry. Being the only mean of rapid global transportation, airlines are driven to attract customers by offering the best prices possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Strength Classifier: Is it really safe?</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Password strength measures how well a password can withstand being guessed or hacked. External attacks can come in the form of password cracking or brute-force attacks, which aim to gain unauthorized access to a computer system or network.
The strength of a password is typically measured by its complexity, length, and unpredictability. Unfortunately, cybercrimes and data breaches have been increasing, and a big reason for this is that passwords are often compromised and weak.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
