<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Visualization on Kasun Malwenna</title>
    <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/tags/data-visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Visualization on Kasun Malwenna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/tags/data-visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tableau Dashboard for COVID-19 Vaccination</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>For this project, I made an interactive dashboard in Tableau to examine and show the most recent COVID-19 vaccination stats.
The data is open to the public and recently obtained from ourworldindata.org and consists of the newest figures from different governments and health organizations all around the world. The per capita measurements were based on a UN study - the World Population Prospects. Income groups were based on the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sport Trading Card Market Analysis for ALT</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Sports trading cards can be considered an alternative investment opportunity as the market for these cards can be relatively stable (especially following the pandemic) and can offer a potential for high returns. The value of a card is often determined by its rarity, condition, and the popularity of the athlete featured on the card. Some high-value cards have sold for millions of dollars. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the market for sports cards can be highly speculative and illiquid, and like any other investment, it carries risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recognize Trading Cards With AI: Industry Project for ALT</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>The sports trading card industry refers to the market for trading cards featuring professional athletes and teams. These cards can be collected, traded, and sold by fans, and they can also be used to play various games and simulations.The popularity of sports trading cards saw a resurgence following the COVID-19 pandemic, as many people turned to collecting as a hobby while stuck at home. With sports events and games being cancelled or played without live audiences, fans turned to collecting cards as a way to stay connected to their favorite teams and athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight Fare Prediction: Let&#39;s Find the Best Rates</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Due to the recent global pandemic, prices of air travel have increased significantly, causing financial challenges for airlines worldwide. As a result, travel disruptions have ensued, leading to 2.3 million job losses in the aviation sector. Prior to the pandemic, air tickets were already subject to price fluctuations due to the competitiveness of the aviation industry. Being the only mean of rapid global transportation, airlines are driven to attract customers by offering the best prices possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Strength Classifier: Is it really safe?</title>
      <link>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KasunMalwenna.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Password strength measures how well a password can withstand being guessed or hacked. External attacks can come in the form of password cracking or brute-force attacks, which aim to gain unauthorized access to a computer system or network.
The strength of a password is typically measured by its complexity, length, and unpredictability. Unfortunately, cybercrimes and data breaches have been increasing, and a big reason for this is that passwords are often compromised and weak.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
